Guide to the James A. Roberts Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1999-290
  - 7023.35 Implementation & monitoring (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - 7023.36 Keller Canyon CPD (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - 00491 EDCWA/WRP/El Dorado County File Index (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - 00491.00.000 General (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - 00491.00 J&S correspondence (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - 00491.00.002 Correspondence out (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - 00491.00.003 Teleconferences (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - 00491.00.004 Articles (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - 00491.00.011 Meetings, Hearings Agenda notes (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - 00491.00.100 EDID Environmental Conservation Selection Process #1 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - 00491.00.100 miscellaneous reports & correspondence (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - 00491.00.120a GEMS contract (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - 00491.00.120b J&S contract #1 1991 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - 00491.00.120b J&S contract #2 1992 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - 00491.00.140 Cost/Time Schedules (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - 00491.00.150 Insurance (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - 00491.00.200 Initial Study (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - 00491.00.700 EIR program description (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - 00491.00.701 Setting Sections (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - 00491.00.702 Bibliography (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - 00491.00.703 Reference (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - 00491.00.704 Air Quality (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - 00491.00.705 Biological Resources (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - 00491.00.706 Traffic (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - 00491.00.707 Hydrology (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - 00491.00.708 Cultural Resources (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - 00491.00.805 Archeological Resources (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - 00491.00.709 Wetlands (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - 00491.00.800 DEIR Water Program (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - 00491.00.801 DEIR comments (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - 00491.00.802 GEMS DEIR review (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - 00491.00.803 GEMS comments response (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - 00491.00.804 FEIR comments (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - 00491.00.805 GEMS FEIR review (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - 00491.00.806 Findings (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - 00491.00.807 General Plan (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - 00491.00.808 EDID/EDCWA (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - 00491.01.00 General (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - 00491.01.120 Contract (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - 00491.01.300 EDID/EDCWA Water Rights Hearing (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - 00491.01.02 General (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - 00491.02.100 RFP (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - 00491.02.120 Contract (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - 00491.03.100 General (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - 00491.03.110 GEMS Proposal (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - 00491.03.120a GEMS contract (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - 00491.03.120b EIP Scope (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - 00491.03.400 Proposal Review (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - 00491.03.401 EIP Baseline charts (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - 00491.03.402 CVP EIS/EIR comments (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - 00491.05.000 Scoping Report (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - 00491.05.110 Scoping contract (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - 00491.05.05 Notice of Presentation (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - 01090 Battelle 1993 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - 01090 Waste systems division 1990 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - 01090 Roberts (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - 01090 Management assistance (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - 01090 Market analysis, progress reports, etc. (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - 01090 Contract & Billing (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - 01090.02 2nd workshop (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - 01090.02.000 General Task 2 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - 01090.02.001 correspondence in (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - 01090.02.002 correspondence out (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - 01090.02.120 Contract (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - 01090.02.02 Waste Processing Engineering Department (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - 04993.00.000 Alaska General (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - 04993.00.000 RFP & Related (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - 01291 EDID correspondence in 1992 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - 01291 correspondence out (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - 01291 Meeting notes (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - 01291 EIR draft report & appendices (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - 01291 Contract (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - 01291 Wetlands Delineations (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - 01291 Wetlands mitigation (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - 01291 Streambed Alteration Agreement (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - 01291 NOP/IS Scoping (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - 01291 SWRCB (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - 01291 Draft Text ESAs (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - 01291 ESA Contract (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - 01291 Negative December Question rates (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - 01291 Traffic (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - 01291 EIR Review (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - 01291 Alternatives/Analysis (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - 01291 Findings (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - 01291 Conditions (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - 01291 Proposals (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - 01291 Miscellaneous Subcontracts etc. (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - 01491 Bernau Wetlands Contract (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - 01491 General (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - 01691 Chelshire downs 1992 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - 01791 77th Ave. (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 8-9/1993 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 10-11/1993 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 12/1993 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 1/1994 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 2-4/1994 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 4-5/1994 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 4-5/1994 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 6-9/1994 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Roberts Chronological correspondence 10-12/1994 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - 01190 Iceland Myvatn Contract (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - 01190 Correspondence out (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - 01190 Correspondence in (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - 01190 EIA Next Steps (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - 01190 TDRs (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - 01190 MEA Preliminary outline (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - 01190 Preliminary Research (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - 01190 Collateral (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - 01190 Trip 3-4/1992 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - 01190 Proposal Revision (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - 01190 Meeting notes (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - 01190 Miscellaneous (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - 01190 Budget work Plans (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - 01190 ECS Constraints & Sensitivities (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - 01190 Alternatives (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - EIR examples, typewritten (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Roberts parkway notebooks (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Humbug Creek/Willow Creek parking plan (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - South Natomas (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Auburn Aeolla Heights I8 1988 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - SSC (Supercolliding Superconductor) I4 1988 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - SSC I5: proposal, contractual (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - SSC I5: contract (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - California Environmental Data Report 1976 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Yosemite Hotel Services Prospectus 1992 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Hawaii C1: Pele Defense Fund 1988 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Hawaii C1: Pele Defense Fund Religion Case (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Hawaii C1: Barbers Point Project Description (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Hawaii C1: Trip 1988 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Hawaii C1: Calls For Action (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Hawaii C1: Roberts July Site Work (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Hawaii C1: Roberts Oct./Nov. Site work (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Hawaii C2: EIS guidelines & related (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Hawaii C2: Kahololawe (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Hawaii C2: Environmental Center (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Hawaii C2: CREDAA general (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Hawaii C2: Economics (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Hawaii C2: Pele Defense Fund Barber’s Point Intervention (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Hawaii C3: Geology (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Hawaii C3: 1985 Eruption (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Hawaii C3: Biology (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Hawaii C3: Alternatives (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Hawaii C3: Food Irradiation (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Hawaii C3: Air Quality (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Hawaii C3: Cable general (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Hawaii C3: Shore Waters & Shores Rules Summary (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Hawaii C4: Cumulative Impacts (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Hawaii C4: HEP study (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Hawaii C4: Pele Defense Fund Land Exchange (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Hawaii C4: Articles (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Hawaii C4: Don Hallock (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Hawaii C4: Geothermal (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - MCP I1: reports etc. 1988 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - MCP I1: Transportation Statistics Study (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - MCP I2: Golder Contract & Bills (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - MCP I2: chronological correspondence 2-4/1988 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - MCP I2: management notes (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - MCP I2: chronological correspondence 9/1988- (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - MCP I2: chronological correspondence 5-8/1988 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - MCP I3: to dos (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - MCP I3: to dos (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - 990 Summit engineering 1990 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - 960 CEQA 7026-960 1991 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - 1100 CEQA coordination 7026-1100 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Sonoma/Napa Landfills (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - 1000 MRF general 7026-1000 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - 961 CEQA process (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - EIR examples: Sonoma County 1988-1991 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Risk Assessment Guide, Material Safety Datasheets Golder (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - MCP DEIR 1989-1990 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - MCP reports & related 1989-1990 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Nevada County: Resource Conservation (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Nevada County: Department of Sanitation, Solid Waste division (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Nevada County: Department of Sanitation, Waste water Division (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Nevada County: Sheriff (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Nevada County: Department of Social Services MEA (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Nevada County: STAR (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Nevada County: Superior Court (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Nevada County: Department of Transportation (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Nevada County: Transportation commission (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Nevada County: Treasurer/Taxes (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Nevada County: School Districts (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Nevada County Agencies: County Administration (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Nevada County Agencies: Agricultural Commissioner (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Nevada County Agencies: Assessor (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Nevada County Agencies: Building Inspector (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Nevada County Agencies: Community Action Agency (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Nevada County Agencies: Committee on Aging (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Nevada County Agencies: Clerk (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Nevada County Agencies: District Attorney (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Nevada County Agencies: Counsel (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Nevada County Agencies: Environmental Health (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Nevada County Agencies: Librarian (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Nevada County Agencies: Mental Health (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Nevada County Agencies: Municipal Courts (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Nevada County Agencies: Probation (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Nevada County Agencies: Public Health (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Nevada County: Fire Districts (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Nevada County: Water Sewer Public Utilities Districts (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Nevada County: Miscellaneous Agencies (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Nevada County: State & Federal Agencies (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Nevada County: MEA (Master Environmental Assessment) TOC (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Nevada County: MEA Summary (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Nevada County: MEA Geology/Soil (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Nevada County: MEA Air Quality (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Nevada County: MEA Public Services (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Nevada County: MEA Archeology/Historic (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Nevada County: MEA Persons contacted (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Nevada County: MEA Bibliography (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Nevada County: MEA Interview Notes (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Nevada County: MEA Information Form (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Nevada County: MEA Appendices (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Nevada County: MEA Comment Responses (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Nevada County: MEA GEMS- Leilani (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Nevada County: MEA Miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Nevada County: MEA Nevada City Planning (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Nevada County: MEA Nevada City General Information (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Nevada County: MEA Resource Conservation (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Nevada County: MEA Grass Valley (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Nevada County: MEA Miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 1990 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence: Steve McHugh 1990 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence: Christmas Letter 1990-1991 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence: Book 2 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - NAEP, other professional organizations G1 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - GEMS soft analysis (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - GEMS general correspondence G2 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - GEMS general correspondence, bios G3 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - GEMS qualifications (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - GEMS-Golder correspondence (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - GEMS Bank (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - GEMS Office (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - GEMS General Correspondence (Box 83, Folder 32)
  - GEMS Business Documents (Box 83, Folder 33)
  - GEMS Miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 34)
  - Golder SoQ material G4 1988 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Golder (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Golder memoranda, notes, correspondence (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - 0491.04.120 Contract/Litigation reviews (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - 0491.04.000 General (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - 0491.04 Program Challenges (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Nevada County General Plan Draft 1993 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Iceland A6 1990 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Iceland A6: Reykjavik Master Plan 1984 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Iceland A7 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Iceland A8 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Iceland A8: Central Bank of Iceland Iceland Handbook 1986 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Hungary/Eastern Europe 1991 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Emerging Europe 1991 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - SWRCB Toxic Waste Reports 1988-1990 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Sacramento Centrage Project Reports 1989 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous reports, directories (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - State of California contracts (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Elsmere DEIR technical appendices 1995 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - 94031 FTB project working documents 1992-1995 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - SFAR background maps (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Tahoe Soil Survey (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - EDCWA SWRCB testimony 1993 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - EDCWA comments 1992 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - EDCWA comments (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - American River Watershed Project daft supple. Report 1995 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - MCP DEIR appendices v.2 1989 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - MCP EIR response documents 1990 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - California Water Plan (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - SSC reports 1987-1988 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Santa Rosa Waste Water DEIR 1990 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - EDID 1993-1995 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Folsom Master Plan files #1 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Folsom Master Plan files #2 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Folsom Master Plan files #3 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - EIR examples: Oakland, Texas 1986-1994 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence ending 12/1991 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 1-4/1992 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 5-8/1992 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 9-10/1992 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 11-12/1992 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 1-2/1993 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 3-4/1993 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 5-6/1993 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Roberts chronological correspondence 7/1993 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - El Dorado County EDID/EDCWA reports (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - El Dorado County EDID/EDCWA reports (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - EIR examples: Roblar Roads DEIR 1987; B&J Landfill 1992; American River Crossing 1992 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - EIR examples: American River Crossing; Sacramento 1990; Willow Springs (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous magazines & Newsletters (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - NAEP board meeting minutes, notes, memoranda 1993-1995 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - NAEP board meetings 1995-1996 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - EIR examples: Sacramento 1988- 1993; Intel 1989; Nevada County 1986-1992; California Secretary of State/State Archives 1988; Auburn 1985; B&J Landfill 1992; Cache Creek 1981; Roberts: Del Monte Forest 1973; Covell Park 1972 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - EIR examples: Broadstone 1990; California Department of Corrections 1994 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Roberts reprints 1995 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Association of American Geographers newsletter 1992-1994 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - reSources, Non-Profit Resource Center newsletter (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - American Planning Association 1994-1997 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Asia Business Opportunities (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Sacramento Chamber of commerce Handbook 1994-1995 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Roberts resumes F6: African Methodist University 1987 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Roberts resumes F6: Brochure ideas (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Roberts resumes F6: articles (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Roberts resumes F6: 1990 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Roberts resumes F6: Other resumes (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Roberts resumes F6: Backup (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Roberts resumes F6: C.V. & related (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - People & Contacts F5 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - People & Contacts F5: international (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - People & Contacts F5: correspondence (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - People & Contacts F5: Information Requests (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - California Heritage Preservation Committee meeting 1990 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - California Integrated Waste Management Planning etc. (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Photographs (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - San Juan Unified School District Budget committee 1987-1988 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - School Board Vacancy Ad Hoc Committee (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - 00690.28 city of Folsom File index (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - 00690.28 92-01 Briggs Ranch Commercial (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - 00690.28 92-01 Briggs (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - 00690.28 92-03 Blue Ravine (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - 00690.28 92-04 Bridge (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - 00690.28 92-05 Broadstone II (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - 00690.28 92-05 Broadstone II (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - 00690.28 92-06 Mitigation Monitoring (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - 00690.28 92-07 Humbug/ Willow Creek (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - 00690.28 92-09 Teichert #2 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - 00690.28 92-09 Teichert #1 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - 00690 Blue Ravine reports, etc. (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - 00690 Miscellaneous reports (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Hazardous Waste Management H4 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Roberts presentations: “Just What is EIR?” 1/1992 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Roberts presentations: “Think Globally” 6/1992 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Roberts presentations: “The Environmental Ethic” 1/1992 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Roberts presentations: “Some Good News” 5/1992 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Roberts presentations: “Towards an Environmental Ethic” 1/1992 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Roberts presentations: SOS 1991 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Roberts presentations: Association of Pacific Coast Geographers conference 1987 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Roberts presentations: “Just What is EIR?” Rotary Club 10/1991 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Roberts presentations: SMUD (Sacramento Municipal Utility District) teachers 4/1991 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Roberts presentations: International Congress of Surveyors 1974 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Roberts presentations: Arizona Planning Association conference 10/1988 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Roberts presentations: Geographers work 6/1992 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Roberts presentations: Leif the Unlucky 1991 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - EIR examples: Kerr-McGee; Mammoth & Sofar I7 1973-1987 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Mineral Management H6 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Environmental Education Curriculum (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - California Department of Corrections Preproposal Conference Vol.2 1995 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Hazardous Materials & Solid Waste Regulations 1990-1994 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Water Quality legislation (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - NAFTA reports (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Sacramento Zoning (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - California Legislative Assembly Bills 1993 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - EIR examples: Hercules Refinery 1992; Continental Plaza 1993; Sacramento Light Rail Extension 1992; Sacramento General Plan Update 1987; Golden state Tower 1989; Capitol Mall Office Complex 1988; State Prison Emergency Bed Project 1995; Capitol Towers 1993; W. Sacramento Triangle 1992 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Water Right Decision 1992 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Richmond Machine & Fabricating Gas Flare Tower 1989 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Chevron Plant 1993 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - 93063 California & Nevada Navy Base Closures (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - 93062 Sierra Bravo (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - 93061 CTC (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - 93059 Carmichael Water District ESA (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - 93055 Vanuatu Urban Infrastructure (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - 93054 Talinn Botanical Garden (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - 93053 Cove East (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - 93052 Orange County (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - 93050 Intel Permit Coordination (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - 93045 Placer County Landfill (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Hungary (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - State Contracts- Qualifications (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Asia General B6: Saipan 1/1989 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Asia General B6: Asia Development Bank (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Asia General B6: Contracts (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Asia General B6: Mariana, Saipan, etc. (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Asia General B7: Philippines conference 1988 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Asia General B7: Taiwan Theme Park (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Asia General B7: Philippines 11/1988 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Asia General B7: Asian Business Development publications 1988 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - International- Other E8: Hawaii trip 1988 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - International- Other E8: England-Scotland Trip 1986 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Chevron Comment Responses 1993 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Shell Martinez Risk Upset analysis vol.5 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Crockett Cogeneration 1992 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Shell Comment Responses 1993 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - EDCWA draft final supplement (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Chevron miscellaneous drafts, correspondence, memoranda (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Chevron reports (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Taiwan D4: maps, correspondence, reports (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Land management/Real Estate Symposium 6/1989 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Taiwan D5: maps, correspondence, publications (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Taiwan D6 1981 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Taiwan D6: Asia Foundation follow-up (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - 00690 City of Folsom .01.5-.04b File Index (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - 00690.01.5 Highway 50 Improvements (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - 00690.01.6 Willow Springs (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - 00690.01.7 Joint Powers Authority (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - 00690.01.8 Regional Transit (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - 00690.01.9 TDRs (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - 00690.01.10 College Site (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - 00690.01.12 Findings (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - 00690.01.13 EAFP Promontory (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - 00690.01.1B Silverbrook Specific Plan #2 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - 00690.01.1B Reflections II (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - 00690.04.1B Reflections (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - 00690.04 Sante Fe #1 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - 00690.04 Sante Fe #2 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - 00690 Box 1-9 File Index (Complete) (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - 00690 General Administration #1 1991 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - 00690 #2 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - 00690.00 Contract (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - 00690.00 Task Orders, Full Set 12/1992 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - 00690.00 Intel (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - 00690.00 Prison Industrial Authority (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - 00690.00 Source Reduction, Recycling (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - 00690.00 TSM (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - 00690.00 Natoma Station, Etc. (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - 00690.00 Preselected Consultants (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous reports: avalanches, earthquakes, geothermal resources 1977-1991 (Box 102, Folder 17)